[{
    "theme": "游띫 Llegando a Espa침a",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "How do you say 'Good morning'?",
            "answers": ["Buenos d칤as"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'We are going to Santiago de la Ribera'?",
            "answers": ["Vamos a Santiago de la Ribera"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Is there a bus that goes there?'",
            "answers": ["쮿ay un autob칰s que va all칤?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Yes, bus number 17 goes to la Ribera'?",
            "answers": ["S칤, el autob칰s n칰mero 17 va a la Ribera"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The bus stop is to the right'?",
            "answers": ["La parada de autob칰s est치 a la derecha"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say '... when leaving the airport'?",
            "answers": ["... al salir del aeropuerto"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Can I go by taxi?'",
            "answers": ["쯉e puede ir tambi칠n en taxi?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Of course'?",
            "answers": ["Claro que s칤"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'We will be late 15 minutes'?",
            "answers": ["Vamos a tardar quince minutos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'How long is the bus ride?'",
            "answers": ["쮺u치nto tiempo tarda el autob칰s?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'About half an hour'?",
            "answers": ["Una media hora"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'How much is the bus ticket?'",
            "answers": ["쮺u치nto cuesta el billete de autob칰s?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The bus tickets cost 1.40 euros'?",
            "answers": ["Los billetes de autob칰s cuestan 1 euro con cuarenta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The taxi costs between 10 and 15 euros'?",
            "answers": ["El taxi cuesta entre 10 y 15 euros"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Very good'?",
            "answers": ["Muy bien"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I think we will take a taxi'?",
            "answers": ["Creo que vamos a coger un taxi"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'More comfortable and faster'?",
            "answers": ["M치s c칩modo y m치s r치pido"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The bus is less comfortable'?",
            "answers": ["El autob칰s es menos c칩modo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say '... and less fast'?",
            "answers": ["... y menos r치pido"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'More or less'?",
            "answers": ["M치s o menos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am more happy' (male speaker)?",
            "answers": ["Estoy m치s contento"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am more happy' (female speaker)?",
            "answers": ["Estoy m치s contenta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am less happy' (male speaker)?",
            "answers": ["Estoy menos contento"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I am less happy' (female speaker)?",
            "answers": ["Estoy menos contenta"]
        }
    ]
}]
